menupix.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - MenuPix.com - The World's Largest Restaurant Menu Website

## Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy pertains to both aggregate and personally identifiable information collected and/or received by MenuPix.com for users (either registered or unregistered). MenuPix.com displays third party advertisements and links to restaurant and other websites. This Privacy Policy does not pertain to third-party advertisements placed on MenuPix.com or websites linked from MenuPix.com; these companies usually have their own Privacy Policy.

## Information Collection and Use

When you register, you provide us with personal information such as your email address, name, age, gender, and zip code. Registration is voluntarily and is not required to use MenuPix.com; however registration allows users to create customized views and take advantage of other features and offers.

We may use this information to customize the advertising you see. We may also from time to time provide third-party offers, coupons, and other marketing email or other correspondence; however, users may opt-out of promotional offers at the time of registration or at any other time by editing their personal options.

Like most websites, MenuPix.com automatically records your IP address and your activity within MenuPix.com. This information contributes to aggregate information such as the number of total visits, unique visitors, unique visits, page view, hits, and which pages were accessed. We may also utilize this information to help manage the website and identify potential problems. We collect some information about our users that we do not share to better understand our users demographics and what features they like on MenuPix.com. Using the [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads), visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.

We may share aggregate information with our partners or advertisers. We may also use this information to improve the functionality and content of our website or to contact you with important notices or for other administrative purposes.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

## Information Sharing

MenuPix.com does not share, sell, rent, or otherwise distribute your personal information unless you have provided us with your consent or one of the following conditions applies:

  * To provide you with a product or service you have requested.
  * We are working with a vendor under confidentiality agreements in order to provide communication from MenuPix.com or one of our partners. These companies do not have the right to use or share this information in any way except as directed by MenuPix.com.
  * To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or to establish or exercise our legal rights, or defend against legal claims or as otherwise required by law.
  * To investigate or take action (preventative or otherwise) regarding any suspected illegal activities, fraud, or violations of MenuPix.com Terms of Use.
  * To transfer your information in the event of a merger with or acquisition by another company. If this occurs, we will notify you in advance and provide you with the new Privacy Policy.

Our banner advertisements and other advertisements are sometimes targeted towards specific demographics. In these cases, your personal information may be used to target ads, but your specific information is never shared with the advertisers in any way. Note that by clicking on an advertisement on MenuPix.com, an advertiser may make the assumption that you fit into a predefined demographic.

## Cookies

MenuPix.com uses cookies to track and enhance activity on the site. Some uses include recognizing and identifying registered users, MyMenuPix settings, unique visitors and visits, and the last city visited for both registered and unregistered users. In addition, third party advertisers may utilize cookies. Their use of cookies is subject to their own Privacy Policy; however, they do not have access to MenuPix.com’s cookies. You can disable cookies on most web browsers. If you disable cookies, your access to MenuPix.com and many other websites may be limited.

## Data Security

Access to your personal information is limited to employees that have a reasonable and relevant need for that information in order to perform their duties. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in place to protect your personal information as well as our other information and data.

## Update Account Information or Delete Account

Registered users can log into MenuPix.com at anytime and edit their personal information and/or opt out of promotional offers. To delete an account, users should email us at [support@menupix.com](mailto:support@menupix.com). While we will delete an account from our active database(s) upon request, this information may still exist in our data archives.

## Children

MenuPix.com does not allow registration for users under 13 years old. For users under 18 years old, we ask that a parent or guardian create an account and monitor the account access. We will not contact children under 13 for marketing purposes or knowingly collect or maintain personal information for children under 13 years old.

## Opt Out

MenuPix.com does not sell, share, or otherwise disseminate personal information unless consent is provided. During the registration process, users may select whether they would like to receive newsletters, promotional offers, coupons, and/or other materials from MenuPix.com and/or third parties. After registering, users may change these options at anytime and edit other personal information.

We reserve the right to send certain emails regarding new service offerings or other administrative issues without providing an opt-out option.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

MenuPix.com reserves the right to makes changes to our Privacy Policy. In the event there is a significant change to our policy or the way we collect or treat your personal information, we will place a notification on our website. Links to our current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use can be found at the bottom of each webpage on MenuPix.com

## Questions and Suggestions

Feel free to email us with questions about our Privacy Policy at [support@menupix.com](mailto:support@menupix.com)
